I'm curious to know, you're talking about the money funding these Antifa organizations
and somebody brought up Roy Singham, I think it was you, who by the way is married to one
of the co-founders of Code Pink, this infamous left-wing organization.
I'm curious to know the administration's-
Who is that?
Roy Singham, he's married to-
No, did you say they're here?
No, he's not.
A journalist brought him up, but he is.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Yeah.
Jameis, thank you.
Good.
I'm curious to see somebody who's been reported on extensively and I'd love to know what the
administration is going to do to actually bring consequences to some of these names
you mentioned.
Well, I don't know the name, but I would like to ask Pam to take a look at it.
You know, a lot of the best information we find are through you and other people like
you.
So, I'd like you to look at it, Pam.
In the back, please.
It's been actually very compelling proof that Antifa did infiltrate on January 6th, dressed
up like Trump supporters and incited violence.
Is that something that you would want the new J6 committee at Congress to look into?
Well, I've heard that.
They dress up like, you know, they're fresh out of MAGA, but they have nothing to do with
MAGA and they make trouble and they try and blame it.
And yeah, we know some of that and we will be acting on some of that.
We've seen it.
Well, I think you could say a little longer, but, you know, the problem is, although you
have some very honest journalists in here, you also have some mostly, largely dishonest
journalists like MSDNC and CNN.
I think they're very dishonest, unbelievably, like a waste of time even talking to them.
But I have to go now to try and solve some problems in the Middle East, although I'm
very well represented by our Secretary of State.
He could probably do an even better job than me.
But who knows?
We don't want to take any chances.
So we're going to go and do that.
If you'd like, Pam, would you like to stay for another five minutes, ten minutes while
we have all these great people?
And I'll let Pam and Christy take over and get some good points out.
I just want to thank the people around the table in particular.
You've been amazing.
You've been brave.
You're real patriots.
And at some point, we're going to have to look into, at least in certain cases, rewarding
you with some very important medals and honors, okay, as we have done.
And we'll be doing with Charlie Kirk.
You know, Charlie is getting the Presidential Medal of Freedom, which is our highest award
outside of the Congressional Medal of Honor.
And I think there's sort of even one's civilian and one's military.
But unfortunately, the civilian sometimes is military also because of what we have to
go through on the streets of this country.
I can only tell you this.
We have a great nation.
We have a nation that's right now the hottest in the entire world.
We're the hottest nation in the world, despite all of the things we've been saying today.
But that's going to make your job easier because nobody's doing better than we are financially.
We've never done better.
We've had, I think, 58 stock market increases since I've been top, meaning record increases.
We have never seen anything like it.
And we're going to keep it going.
That makes it a little bit easier for what we're doing.
I guess maybe it also makes some people crazy because they don't want to see us do well.
But we're the hottest nation anywhere in the world, and we were a dead nation one year
ago.
I say it all the time.
We were a dead nation.
Now we're the hottest nation in the world.
And that's said, too, by every leader.
One of the reasons that we have every country already signed up or just about to sign, every
country in the world on this whole mess we have going over with Hamas and the Middle
East and all of the things you see is they respect our nation.
A year ago, you wouldn't have been able to get it.
You certainly couldn't have gotten it with Biden.
You didn't know where the hell he was.
But a year ago, you wouldn't have been able to have a situation like this.
So I just want to thank the people around this table and certainly the officials around
the table because they've been incredible.
They've been brave.
And I watched yesterday, Pam, and I watched a little bit.
I thought it was so good.
I rounded up and I watched it late in the evening because I thought you were fantastic
yesterday.
You really, look, we had some wonderful senators, some great politicians asking you very fair
questions and you had some real, real slime balls.
But I thought you were amazing.
So thank you very much.
And Christy, thanks for the great job.
Cash, thanks for the great job.
Always my man back down there.
He's the silent type, but he's a hell of a lawyer.
Thank you all.
We're going to get we're going to get peace in the Middle East.
That's what we want to do.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Just listening as President Trump wrapping up, taking questions from reporters, talking
about Antifa, different independent journalists, conservative activists, YouTubers, podcasters
in attendance.
There's President Trump walking out of the room, shaking their hands, talking about some
of their interactions in Portland, Oregon, Austin, Texas, Los Angeles, Southern California,
and the like.
As you can see there alongside Attorney General Pam Bondi and others.
And you also saw inside of that room of President Trump sharing a note with Secretary of State
Marco Rubio, potential developments about the ongoing happenings in the war in Gaza,
potentially closer to a ceasefire than ever.
You can see this from Jackie Heinrich saying President Trump saying he may travel to the
Middle East late Saturday and Sunday, if all goes well, finalizing the last few details
on this Israel-Hamas deal to end the war in Gaza.
We did see Secretary of State Marco Rubio walk into the room, pass a note over to President
Trump about this such conversation.
So obviously some developments in terms of this from Marco Rubio.
Jennifer Griffin, though, as Fox has told Secretary Rubio, no longer traveling to Paris
tomorrow.
A lot of moving pieces in the Middle East, I am told this is developing and potentially
the fact that Rubio not going to be in Paris, a good sign for this deal.